(THE YARNS)
Scientific criminal forgery
of population registration certificate.
Gratitude!
The mysterious grateful person might mean...
Popular teen star Tali Danuwat has killer genes.
And then you notice this red light.
If the red light is blinking,
it means that you are under the police's sight.
You will be safe.
Fah!
The police are coming!
It's my fault, I couldn't finish him off.
This time it's definitely my turn.
That low-life bastard must pay.
To show responsibility,
I would like to resign as party leader
and prime ministerial candidate
from today onwards.
That low-life bastard.
"P TRAIKANON"
What message does Fah want to send
if she wants to kill me?
Does Lan have any other family members
whose names start with P?
Is that...
Who are you?
Aren't you putting a bounty on my head?
The Yarn Murderer.
Let go, let me go!
I told you to let me go!
I thought that when we first met,
there would be something better to say than this.
Do have any clue...
about who I am?
I do.
I know you so well.
You low-life bastard!
What do you mean?
Look at my face.
Who do you miss?
I don't know.
I told you to think it through.
I said I don't know!
I've never seen your face before.
Do whatever you want to do.
If you want to kill me, kill me!
But I'm warning you.
If I die,
you won't get away with this.
If the police are really competent,
I wouldn't have killed ten people.
And if you wait for your
beloved police son to save you,
I've tricked him to somewhere else already.
Fah!
Where are you?
Let me go! I'm going to kill him!
Let me go!
You'll find out soon
about who I am.
Fah!
Where are you? Where are you?
Let me go! I'm going to kill him!
Let me go now, Fah!
Where is he?
Let me go! I'm going to kill him!
- Let me go. Let me go.
- I'll take you there.
I'll take you there.
Don't do anything to him yet.
You have to believe me, Mom.
Believe you. Believe you.
I'm going to kill him.
I'm going to kill him. I'm going to kill him.
Let go.
Who is that?
It's Anna, sir.
Get me the booze.
You've had too much to drink, sir.
I think you should go rest.
Come on. I will help you get there.
Go get some booze.
I told you to go get some booze. Go get some booze!
Let go!
- Let go!
- Anna!
Anna.
What's going on? It was so loud.
He wanted to have another drink,
but I think he was already too drunk.
Oh, Mr. Pitak, please stop him.
I've tried to stop him many times,
he will never listen.
So...
Are we just going to leave him like this?
Try to look from his perspective. He's grieving.
It's hard for anyone to accept.
Honestly, if it were me,
I also have to drink to forget
about all the horrible things.
But...
Anne.
Did you hear what Pitak said?
Go get me the booze. Quick!
Just do whatever pleases him.
The booze is here, sir.
Quick.
Tonight, I'd like to rest at home.
Please take care of him.
Mr. Pitak.
Um, it's really late now.
I...
Can I go home?
I'm afraid that my parents will worry.
Then what should we do? Leave him alone?
The other maids have all gone home for Songkran's.
And if something bad happens to him,
what will you do?
Come on, help me.
I have been taking care of him for many nights now.
I want to go home and get a good night's sleep.
Just one night.
Call your parents now.
It's dangerous to go home now.
Let him drink.
When he has enough he will fall asleep
and then you can rest in the guest room.
Tomorrow when I get here,
you can go home.
Okay?
-But...
-Consider this my request.
Okay.
Thank you.
Sir, please let me wipe you clean.
Nisa.
Come back to me.
Please let me wipe your hands.
Nisa?
Please let go of my hand. It's Anna.
Nisa. Nisa.
- Nisa, you've come back to me.
- It's Anna! Let go!
Let go of me!
Let go! This is Anna!
Nisa! Nisa!
Let go! Let go!
- Nisa!
- Let go!
Let me go!
Nisa.
Long time no see.
Let me go!
Nisa.
The low-life bastard!
Let me go, I'll kill him!
I'm gonna kill him! Let me go! He raped me!
Anna.
Fah, let me go! I'm going to kill him!
I'll kill him! I'll kill him!
You said you would listen to me.
- I'll kill him.
- Mom.
You said you would listen to me.
- Let me go, I'll kill him!
- Mom, didn't you say you would listen to me?
I'll let you kill him for sure.
But I want to get my revenge first.
- Mom, calm down first.
- I'll kill him.
Let me go, I'll kill him.
Anna.
Are you still alive?
- Then why are you like this?
- Because of you.
You raped my mother until she went mad.
And I am the product of your evil.
I will kill you.
I will kill you. Let go!
What do you mean?
- Are you my daughter?
- Daughter?
How dare you call me a daughter?
Fine.
Father,
I will kill you today.
Kill him. Kill him.
You have to kill him, Fah.
Fah.
You have to kill him. Kill him!
Finish him!
Kill him, Fah!
What are you waiting for?
A person like you has no right
to call me your daughter.
What are you going to do?
Are you scared?
It doesn't hurt.
My whole life has way way
more painful than this.
I was beaten up.
I'm not your mother!
- Where are you going to run to?
- Mom, Mom!
- Fah!
- Mother, please don't beat me.
No one loves me.
No one cares.
Does it hurt? Does it hurt?
You deserve this!
What hurts you is not as bad as
what your father did to your mother!
Then don't ask me again what the horrible fuck
did your father do to your mother!
Because I don't want to think about it anymore.
Do you understand?
Because I am the sin you left behind.
I am sorry.
I didn't mean to hurt Anna.
I was very drunk that night.
And then I sent someone to look for Anna.
I want to take responsibility for what I do.
Bullshit.
For someone like you,
if you really want to find my mother,
it won't be difficult.
My mother screams
and wants to kill you nights and days.
The word "low-life bastard"
echoes in my head all the time.
The low-life bastard.
You evil bastard!
You low-life bastard!
You did it to me!
- You did it to me!
- Anna, Anna.
- You raped me, I'll kill you!
- Anna
- Anna.
- I'll kill you!
And finally...
I have found you.
You low-life bastard!
I'll kill him, you low-life bastard!
Grandma.
I will kill him.
So, do you know who he is?
- I'll kill him.
- I don't know.
Do you have his full name?
I said what I said.
Don't you understand?
I've never even seen his face. Why are you asking?
If you have his name, will you kill him?
- I'll kill him.
- Stop asking.
-Annoying
-I'll kill him.
It is now certain that
Dr. Chonlathorn Traikanon will run
for the position of Prime Minister
on behalf of the Palang Prachathai Progressive Party.
All Thai citizens, brothers and sisters,
please rest assured.
-Anna!
-I'll kill you!
- Mom, mom!
- I'll kill him. I'll kill him!
- I'm gonna kill him! He raped me!
- Anna!
I'm gonna kill him! He raped me!
Mom.
He raped me!
I will kill him.
I remember him, he raped me.
More! Kill him!
Good, Fah. More.
You low-life bastard!
You must die.
Fah, don't stop. Kill him! Give him hell!
I like it, I like it.
Are you scared?
Don't be scared.
I have a light hand.
What a coincidence!
That's the person who raped my mother,
he is the one who sets the rules
to control the killer genes.
Do you know?
Your law has destroyed my dream of becoming a doctor.
I'm going to use this fucking law
destroy your dream of becoming a prime minister.
How do you feel?
My dear Fah.
You did a great job, sweetheart.
I love you the most.
Since I was born...
I did everything to make my mother love me.
But it never worked.
But did you hear that just now?
My mother said she loves me.
I'm so fucking happy.
Don't do this, baby girl.
You have no right to call me your baby girl.
Dad, Sky will go to Dad. Sky will go to Dad.
Huh? Sky? Sky?
- Sky will go to see her dad.
- Sky, you have a dad, baby. You only have me.
This is your mommy.
I have a father.
Sky has a father, the twin is going to kill him.
The twin is going to kill father.
Is Lan's father Sky's father too?
Is that right, Sky?
Yes. Definitely.
If the Officer's father is the twin's father too,
he must also be my father.
- Sky will go see her father.
- Sky, Sky, Sky, listen, honey.
Even if he is, it is dangerous.
Sky, please don't go.
Let the police handle it.
- Please, sweetheart?
- Let Sky help father.
Sky feels sorry for father.
If Dr. Chonlathorn is really Sky and Fah's father,
are we going to let the daughter kill her father?
Sky is worried about her father.
Sky wants to help her father.
Kill him. Kill him, Fah. Just kill him!
Take it easy, mom.
I know how you feel.
But a bastard like him...
he cannot die in peace.
He must die in agony,
just like what you've endured.
Good.
Very good.
I should praise you.
Go ahead!
If I pass the Law to protect the safety of the people
and it makes you resent me this much.
- Go ahead and kill me.
- The safety of the people?
What was it called when you fucking raped my mom?
You don't have the killer genes.
But you still raped my mother.
Your theory was wrong from the start, you asshole!
Why the fuck are you silent all of a sudden?
Tell me, how you are different from a murderer?
Fucking answer me!
I am sorry.
Let me go.
I will take Anna to get treatment.
I will change your
house registration certificate for you.
You will be able to study medicine as you wish.
I will adopt you as my daughter.
I promise you.
I will take good care of you and your mother.
You're abusing your power.
You always claim that you're doing for the people,
in the end, you're just a hypocrite.
It's a blessing
that you're not the Prime Minister of the country.
Today I will do my best,
for me,
for my mother,
for my grandparents, my best friend,
and for everyone who was resented
by society. I will kill you.
You want to know how I'm going to kill you, right?
It's because of you that I can't become a doctor.
I can only operate on mice and frogs and study at home.
Today, please be my lab frog.
That's it. Kill him. Kill him.
Kill him.
No.
I really want to open your skull and see your brain inside.
What part of your brain
did you use to issue that fucking Law?
Stop!
Put the weapon!
Don't come closer.
How did you follow me here?
When you kill your victim,
your anger and resentment have reached Sky.
She can sense everything.
Turn yourself in, Fah.
Do you dare shoot your own little sister?
Younger sister?
Yeah.
I'm your little sister.
If you don't believe me, just ask your father.
Sky.
Are you really sure that the vision you saw
in your mind is Dr. Chonlathorn.
I'm sure.
But he's Lan's father.
If he's the Officer's father,
then he must be mine too.
Let Sky go in. Sky will help father.
Sky will help father.
Sorry, doctor, you cannot enter.
Let Sky go in. Sky will help father.
Officer, please let Sky pass.
Don't forget that Sky is the killer's twin.
Sky can help persuade the killer. Please.
Please.
You know your father's shame now.
Your dear father.
He's as fucked up as me.
Stop it, Fah.
Put an end to this. This is all wrong.
But it was right for you to kill my friend?
It wasn't wrong for your father
to make my mother a living dead?
You are the police.
But you police have never saved the people
who were dehumanized.
Everyone is under the law.
Do you still dare to call it a law
when it can only apply to poor people?
If you want to shoot, shoot me.
Or I'll kill your father.
Twin...
Don't do it, twin!
Don't try to stop me, sister.
You can't stop me.
Who are you?
Why does your face look like Fah?
- Who are you?
- She's another one of your daughters.
Twin daughters born from this low-life bastard!
Daughter?
Mother...
Are you my real Mother?
Daughter?
My daughter...
Do you have another daughter?
Daughter...
Why do I have children? Why?
Why? Why do I have children?
You! You low-life bastard, you raped me!
You raped me! You must die!
You must die!
- Fah...
- Why is mom like this? Why is mom like this?
This fucking bastard made your mom like that!
he ruined my mother's life.
After knowing the truth,
are you still going to stop me?
I am.
Twin, please don't do that.
Sky is begging you.
We will get back together again.
Sky loves her twin.
Sky loves you, little sister.
Thank you.
Even though you don't even know me,
you still love me.
But I have to do it.
They're shooting.
Sky.
You killed my child! You killed my child!
You killed my child!
You killed my child! I will kill you!
Grandmother.
Are you my grandmother?
Fah! Fah!
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry for not raising you well.
I'm sorry, my dear.
Don't cry, grandma.
Don't cry.
This is Sky.
S-K-Y means the space above the Earth.
I'm sorry.
I was the one who made grandpa give you away.
Sky, hug your grandmother, sweetheart.
Comfort her, sweetheart.
Grandma, don't cry.
Don't cry, don't cry.
Sky is here now.
Where is Fah?
The shocking incident occurred
just one day before election day.
The serial killer that the authorities were hunting
broke in and attacked
Dr. Chonlathorn Traikanon,
the former Prime Ministerial Candidate.
He was seriously injured and in a coma.
The culprit that the media has always called the Yarn Murderer is actually Ms. Fahrung Sanguankhun.
She was shot and arrested.
She is currently under medical care with police officers deploying tight security to prevent her escape.
Fah.
(THREE MONTHS LATER)
I will comb your hair.
I will make you pretty.
Grandma.
Which one do you prefer?
Whichever is fine, dear.
Your mother likes blue.
Pick it for her then.
This one is better.
Mom will definitely look beautiful when she wears it.
Beautiful.
Am I beautiful, Fah?
- Ma'am
- Yes.
what did the nurse say about Anna's condition?
Is she getting better?
I don't see her throwing a tantrum anymore.
She doesn't throw a tantrum
because the doctor gave her a sedative.
It will take time to heal.
Please hang in there.
Alright.
I really have to thank you, Ma'am,
for bringing Anna to get treatment,
and also let me live with you.
I really don't know
how to repay your kindness.
It's okay. You are Sky's grandmother too.
You are Sky's grandmother.
Grandmother which means a mother of a mother.
Therefore, Grandma is also Mother Sookwan's mother.
Okay.
It's all over now, Rapee.
I'm sorry.
I didn't take care of you enough.
Please, be happily at peace, Rapee.
I will miss Rapee a lot.
Hello?
Yes, of course.
Inspector.
-Sergeant Moo!
-Sergeant.
- Come on, Sergeant.
- Come on.
Take the middle seat.
- Today I intend to treat you.
- Bring your favorite things, Sergeant.
Thank you.
I thought you would hear
the verdict with us today.
Oh, I can guess. She will be executed for sure.
So I decided to scatter Rapee's ashes today instead.
In fact, it's a shame to waste Fah's genius.
If Fah were to become a doctor by now,
Fah would definitely be a very talented doctor.
Lan, how are Sky and Grandma doing?
Both are saddened.
Everyone could accept that Fah was really wrong.
No one complained or objected.
As for Fah,
she already knew what she put herself into
before she's even started the first crime.
Are you okay?
Nothing.
Let's eat, come on.
Enjoy.
Cheers.
Sky.
Fah does not allow anyone to visit.
She doesn't want to meet anyone.
Officer, can I write a letter to my twin?
I think you can.
Then please wait a moment.
Next is a special press conference by the new Prime Minister
concerning the Laws of controlling killer genes.
For the past serial murders
causing the great loss.
Especially from the families and relatives of the victims.
I and the cabinet
including relevant government officials
would like to express my sincere condolences
to all the deceased's parents and siblings.
The murder incident
led me to revisit and research and find out that
Catherine Vedom's research data,
published in 1977, stated that, "Eventually,
what the killer gene needs is
the desire to be number one, the thirst to win.
If it is used in the right way,
they will be a successful person in their career.
These people are smart and ambitious.
Whether they're doctors, politicians, or the President."
In addition, Professor Jim Fellon,
who discovered the killer gene, said:
"People who have killer genes and don't kill others
are caused by their childhood upbringing.
It can stimulate the genes.
If raised well, they won't become murderers.
On the other hand, if they are not raised well,
being pressured, coerced, or abused,
even without the killer genes,
will eventually become a murderer."
I and the cabinet
have been proposed to repeal
the Law of controlling the killer genes.
And there was a meeting and a unanimous vote,
500 votes with unanimity
have voted to pass the bill
to repeal the killer gene control law
And now, those with killer genes.
They will no longer violate the constitution.
Hold on. Hold on.
Fah.
Why did you do this?
(GRANDMA, I LOVE YOU.
PLEASE TAKE CARE OF MOM. - FAH)
Why did you leave me like this?
Doctor, the documents are ready.
Wait.
What about Mark?
Oh, I heard that he said he had something to do.
He was going to see a girl.
You a-hole!
You chose a girl over work?
Why do you look so angry?
That's nothing. I always talk to him this way.
Let's get started.
Okay, then I'll leave you to it.
Why is the name so strange?
The deceased:
Iloveyousomuch Iloveyouthemost,
25 years old.
Autopsy begins at 2:35 p.m.
-Mark
-Ouch!
-What the hell are you doing?
-It hurts.
How could you joke about work like that?
I will tell the director.
What do you want me to do?
I want to see you, but you keep avoiding me.
You really want to be a corpse, don't you?
What are you doing?
-Stab you to death.
-Are you going to stab me?
Go on, stab me. Stab me in the heart.
Let people know that I died
because my heart was broken.
Cringe.
Do you like it when it's cringe?
Cheesy!
Why are you smiling this big?
I'm not, let go.
Why are you blushing then?
No, I'm not.
Your cheeks are red now.
We're wasting time here. We have work to do.
Let go.
- I won't.
- Let go.
I won't let go until you answer me.
Answer what?
Can I be your fork now?
Can I?
Oh, get down there.
What are you doing?
You want to die, right? You want to die, right?
Anya!
- Do you like it?
- Sure thing!
Go to sleep. Sleep.
Mark?
Do you like it here, Sky?
Yes, I do.
Sky always likes the sky.
It's like my name, S-K-Y, Sky
means the space above the Earth.
You said that you need me to help you decode.
Why did you bring me here?
So where is the code? Is there another new case?
I'm not sure if this is a new case.
But there is a code.
Sky, can you help me decode this?
This is not a code.
It's just a series of numbers without any system.
You must have misunderstood.
No, Sky.
I think there's a hidden code.
Sky, take a good look.
(LAN, I LOVE YOU, SKY)
Where did you get this kind of code? It's funny.
Is that funny?
It's funny
or you're blushing?
It's funny.
And I'm also blushing.
I'm blushing because you're flirting with me.
Sky.
I believe you know the word "girlfriend", don't you?
Sky...
Would you like to be my girlfriend?
What's going on?
It was so loud.
He wanted to have another drink,
but I think he was already too drunk.
Anne.
Go get me the booze. Quick!
Just do whatever pleases him.
The booze is here, sir.
Nisa! Nisa!
Let me go!
Nisa!
Long time no see.
Let me go!
Nisa.